Soviet Union Unregistered Baptists Subject Files, Inclusive: 1948-2011, undated, Bulk: 1960-1989
Baylor University, The Keston Center for Religion, Politics, and Society
- Samizdat, 1961-1987, 2011, undated; 2
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 3 (71), 1980 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 4 (72), 1980 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 1 (73), 1981 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 2 (74), 1981 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 3-4 (75-76), 1981 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 1 (77), 1982 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 2 (78), 1982 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 3 (79), 1982 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 4 (80), 1982 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 1 (81), 1983 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 2 (82), 1983 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 3 (83), 1983 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 4 (84), 1983 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No.4 (84): Extra copy, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 1 (85), 1984 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 1 (85): Extra copy, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 2-3 (86-87), 1984 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 4 (88), 1984 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 1-2 (89-90), 1985 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 3 (91), 1985 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 4 (92), 1985 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 1 (93), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 1 (93): Extra copy, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 2 (94), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 2 (94): Extra copy, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 1 (101), 1988 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 2 (102), 1988 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 3 (103), 1988 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 4 (104), 1988 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 1 (105), 1989 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 2 (106), 1989 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 3 (107), 1989 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 4 (108), 1989 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 1 (109), 1989 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 2, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Vestnik istiny, No. 3, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Activities Disapproved by the State. Underground Production of Religious Literature. Khristianin Publishing House (1 of 2), 1971-1980, undated (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Activities Disapproved by the State. Underground Production of Religious Literature. Khristianin Publishing House (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Schism. Council of Churches of Evangelical Christians and Baptists. Account of a Meeting between CCECB and AUCECB, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Schism. Council of Churches of Evangelical Christians and Baptists. General (1 of 2), 1966-1969 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Schism. Council of Churches of Evangelical Christians and Baptists. General (2 of 2), 1970-1974 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Relations with Fellow Believers, 1970-1982 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Religious Literature. Bible, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Children and Youth, 1968-1974 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Sociology and Family, 1964, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 6)